<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <template id="card_any_type_of_metal_details" name="Any Type of Metal Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Any Type of Metal</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735622876/arizogroup/gvofzizavcu7zqjzk6gj.jpg'"
                                 alt="Any Type of Metal" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">Metals form the foundation of many industries, from
                                    construction
                                    and manufacturing to transportation and technology. With a wide variety of metals
                                    available, it is essential to choose the right one for the job. Whether you're
                                    working with stainless steel, aluminum, copper, or brass, each metal has distinct
                                    properties that make it suitable for specific applications. Our extensive selection
                                    ensures that you have access to high-quality materials that meet your project’s
                                    needs, whether it’s for large-scale construction or intricate manufacturing
                                    processes. We are committed to providing you with the best in terms of quality,
                                    pricing, and service, ensuring that your projects run smoothly.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">One of the key advantages of working with metals is their
                                    durability. Metals are known for their long-lasting strength and resistance to wear
                                    and tear, making them ideal for both indoor and outdoor applications. From the
                                    robustness of steel in structural components to the corrosion resistance of aluminum
                                    in outdoor applications, our metals offer a range of properties that help extend the
                                    life of your products. Additionally, metals are highly versatile, allowing for
                                    various forms such as sheets, rods, and pipes, providing the flexibility needed for
                                    different projects. Our products meet strict industry standards, ensuring that you
                                    can trust them for any task.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">At our store, we don’t just provide raw materials; we offer
                                    expert
                                    advice and support to help you choose the right metal for your specific application.
                                    With our comprehensive inventory and industry expertise, we make the selection
                                    process easier. Our team is dedicated to providing personalized assistance and
                                    ensuring that you have all the necessary information to make informed decisions.
                                    Whether you need a small quantity for a home project or large-scale supplies for
                                    industrial work, we deliver the metals you need when you need them, helping you
                                    achieve the best results every time.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_auto_parts_details" name="Auto Parts Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Auto Parts</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735622877/arizogroup/rx3aauqd3oxlho70owib.jpg'"
                                 alt="Auto Parts" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">

                                <p class="card-text-full">When it comes to auto parts, quality and reliability are
                                    crucial.
                                    At our store, we offer a wide range of auto parts to meet the needs of all vehicle
                                    types, from everyday cars to heavy-duty trucks. Our products include engine
                                    components, transmission parts, suspension systems, electrical systems, and much
                                    more. Each part is carefully sourced from trusted manufacturers, ensuring that you
                                    get durable and dependable components for all your repair and maintenance needs.
                                    With our comprehensive inventory, you can find the right part for your vehicle with
                                    ease.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">In addition to offering quality auto parts, we also provide
                                    competitive pricing and excellent customer service. Our team of experts is available
                                    to guide you in selecting the right components for your specific make and model.
                                    Whether you're a DIY enthusiast or a professional mechanic, we can help you make the
                                    best decision for your vehicle. We understand how important it is to get your
                                    vehicle back on the road quickly, which is why we offer fast and efficient shipping
                                    to ensure that your parts arrive when you need them.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">Beyond providing high-quality products, we also believe in
                                    offering
                                    long-term support. If you're unsure about a part's compatibility or need assistance
                                    with installation, our team is here to help. Our goal is to build long-lasting
                                    relationships with our customers, ensuring that you have access to the best parts
                                    and services whenever you need them. Explore our wide range of auto parts today and
                                    discover why we’re a trusted source for all your vehicle repair and maintenance
                                    needs.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_lawn_equipment_details" name="Lawn Equipment Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Lawn Equipment</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735622875/arizogroup/if81ojdmafetnpmkae4t.jpg'"
                                 alt="Lawn Equipment" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">Maintaining a beautiful lawn requires the right equipment. At
                                    our
                                    store, we offer a wide selection of lawn care tools, including mowers, trimmers,
                                    blowers, and more. Each product is designed to help you achieve a perfectly
                                    manicured lawn with ease. Whether you're looking for a push mower for small lawns or
                                    a riding mower for larger areas, we have equipment that caters to all lawn sizes.
                                    Our high-performance tools ensure a clean, precise cut every time, helping you
                                    maintain a healthy, lush yard throughout the year.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">In addition to lawn mowers, we also offer a variety of other
                                    lawn
                                    care equipment such as leaf blowers, aerators, and hedge trimmers. These tools allow
                                    you to keep your lawn in top condition, making lawn care easier and more efficient.
                                    All our products are designed with durability and ease of use in mind, so you can
                                    spend less time maintaining your equipment and more time enjoying your outdoor
                                    space. We offer equipment from trusted brands, ensuring that you get the best
                                    quality at competitive prices.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">Our goal is to help you choose the right equipment that fits
                                    your
                                    needs. If you're unsure which tools are best for your lawn, our knowledgeable staff
                                    is here to provide expert advice. We can assist with product selection, offer
                                    maintenance tips, and help you get the most out of your investment. Whether you're a
                                    professional landscaper or a homeowner maintaining your garden, we have the tools
                                    you need to make lawn care a breeze.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_aluminium_cans_details" name="Aluminium Cans Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Aluminium Cans</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735623426/arizogroup/eft9rrrmbzlaujzz3c0l.jpg'"
                                 alt="Aluminium Cans" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">Aluminium cans are one of the most commonly used forms of
                                    packaging, especially for beverages. They are lightweight, durable, and recyclable,
                                    making them an environmentally friendly choice. Aluminium is a highly versatile
                                    material, and it is widely used in industries that require lightweight and strong
                                    packaging solutions. At our store, we offer a variety of aluminium cans in different
                                    sizes and designs, all of which are ideal for storing everything from soda and beer
                                    to energy drinks and bottled water.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">The benefits of using aluminium cans go beyond their
                                    eco-friendly
                                    nature. Aluminium is an excellent conductor of heat, which helps to keep beverages
                                    cold for longer periods. The material is also resistant to corrosion and can
                                    withstand the rigors of transportation, ensuring that your products arrive at their
                                    destination in perfect condition. Our aluminium cans come in a variety of finishes,
                                    including smooth, embossed, and matte, offering flexibility for branding and product
                                    packaging.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">We are committed to offering high-quality aluminium cans that
                                    meet
                                    the needs of businesses across various industries. Whether you're looking for cans
                                    for a new product launch or need bulk orders for ongoing production, we can provide
                                    the perfect packaging solution. With our commitment to sustainability, we encourage
                                    recycling and the use of eco-friendly materials to reduce waste and environmental
                                    impact. Choose aluminium cans for your packaging needs and make a sustainable choice
                                    that benefits both your business and the planet.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_cable_wires_details" name="Cable Wires Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Cable Wires</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735622882/arizogroup/dacpzdatbldacffr5pv5.jpg"
                                 alt="Cable Wires" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">Cable wires are a critical component in electrical systems,
                                    used to
                                    transfer electrical current in a safe and efficient manner. Whether you're working
                                    on residential, commercial, or industrial projects, having the right type of cable
                                    is essential to ensure the reliability of your electrical installations. Our range
                                    of cable wires includes options for various applications, including power cables,
                                    communication cables, and specialty wires, all designed to meet the highest
                                    standards of safety and performance. With the right cable, you can be assured of
                                    uninterrupted power supply and minimized electrical hazards.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">We understand that different projects require different types
                                    of
                                    cables, which is why we offer an extensive selection. From low-voltage wires for
                                    household use to high-voltage cables for industrial settings, we provide cables that
                                    suit every need. All of our cables are made from high-quality materials such as
                                    copper and aluminum, ensuring that they offer optimal conductivity and resistance to
                                    wear and tear. Whether you need flexible cables for tight spaces or heavy-duty
                                    cables for industrial machinery, our inventory has the right solutions to meet your
                                    requirements.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">At our store, we not only offer quality cable wires but also
                                    offer
                                    expert advice to help you make the right choice for your project. Our team is
                                    knowledgeable about electrical systems and can provide you with guidance on the best
                                    cable types for specific applications, whether it's wiring a home, setting up a
                                    factory, or creating a complex electrical network. With reliable shipping and bulk
                                    order options, we ensure that you get the cable wires you need on time, making your
                                    projects more efficient and safe. Trust us for your cable wire needs and take
                                    advantage of our expert service and competitive prices.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_plumbing_fixtures_details" name="Plumbing Fixtures and Pipe Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Plumbing Fixtures and Pipe</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735622879/arizogroup/timujpnttq2tpd3xfu0a.jpg'"
                                 alt="Plumbing Fixtures and Pipe" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">Plumbing fixtures and pipes are essential components for any
                                    residential or commercial plumbing system. Whether you’re constructing a new
                                    building or renovating an existing property, having access to high-quality plumbing
                                    materials is crucial for ensuring long-term performance and durability. We offer a
                                    wide selection of plumbing fixtures and pipes, including faucets, showerheads,
                                    sinks, bathtubs, and piping solutions for both water and waste systems. Our products
                                    are sourced from reputable manufacturers and are designed to meet the highest
                                    standards of reliability and quality.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">When it comes to plumbing, the material of the pipes is of
                                    utmost
                                    importance. We offer a variety of pipes made from materials such as PVC, copper,
                                    PEX, and galvanized steel, each suitable for different types of installations. PVC
                                    pipes are perfect for drainage systems, while copper pipes are known for their
                                    reliability in water supply systems. Our range of piping materials is designed to
                                    ensure maximum strength and resistance to corrosion, making them ideal for both
                                    residential and commercial plumbing applications. With the right pipes, you can
                                    avoid leaks and water damage, ensuring a safe and functional plumbing system.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">In addition to pipes, we also offer a variety of plumbing
                                    fixtures
                                    that help create functional and aesthetically pleasing bathrooms and kitchens. From
                                    modern faucets to durable sinks and bathtubs, we have everything you need to enhance
                                    your plumbing system’s performance. Our fixtures come in a wide range of styles and
                                    finishes, ensuring that they complement any design. Whether you’re updating your
                                    home or working on a large-scale commercial project, our plumbing fixtures and pipes
                                    offer both functionality and beauty. Explore our selection today and take the first
                                    step towards creating a high-quality plumbing system.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_electrical_wiring_details" name="Electrical Wiring Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Electrical Wiring</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735622876/arizogroup/uf7yvrfp4htyzkgkffcl.jpg'"
                                 alt="Electrical Wiring" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">Electrical wiring is a fundamental aspect of any electrical
                                    installation. It ensures the safe and efficient distribution of electrical power
                                    across buildings and structures. At our store, we offer a wide range of electrical
                                    wiring options, including low-voltage and high-voltage wires, as well as specialized
                                    wiring for different applications. Whether you're wiring a new construction,
                                    renovating an existing building, or upgrading your current system, we have the right
                                    wiring solutions to suit your needs. Our wiring products are designed to meet the
                                    latest safety standards, ensuring that your electrical systems are both reliable and
                                    secure.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">Our electrical wiring is made from high-quality materials,
                                    including copper and aluminum, which offer excellent conductivity and durability.
                                    Copper wires are particularly well-suited for applications that require
                                    high-performance and long-lasting reliability, while aluminum wires are a
                                    cost-effective alternative for less demanding installations. In addition to standard
                                    wiring, we also provide cables for specialized purposes, such as fire-resistant
                                    cables, underground cables, and cables for high-temperature environments. No matter
                                    what your project entails, we can supply the right wiring to meet the specific
                                    requirements of your electrical system.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">At our store, we go beyond just offering wiring products—we
                                    provide
                                    expert guidance and support to help you choose the right wire for your application.
                                    Our team of professionals is available to answer any questions you have about wire
                                    types, installation methods, and industry standards. We also offer fast shipping and
                                    bulk order options, ensuring that you get the materials you need when you need them.
                                    With our extensive selection of electrical wiring products, you can trust that your
                                    installation will be safe, efficient, and built to last.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_iron_details" name="Iron Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Iron</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735649750/arizogroup/iron-2439297_yh8v0s.jpg'"
                                 alt="Iron" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">Iron is one of the most widely used metals in the world due to
                                    its
                                    versatility and abundance. It is a key material in industries such as construction,
                                    manufacturing, automotive, and more. Iron is valued for its strength, durability,
                                    and ability to be easily fabricated into a wide variety of shapes and sizes. Whether
                                    used in structural components like beams and frames, or in the production of tools
                                    and machinery, iron plays an integral role in the infrastructure that supports
                                    modern life. At our store, we offer a wide selection of iron products for various
                                    applications, including rods, bars, sheets, and castings.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">One of the major advantages of iron is its ability to be
                                    easily
                                    alloyed with other metals, such as carbon, to create materials like steel, which
                                    further enhance its properties. Steel, which is made by adding carbon to iron, is
                                    stronger, more durable, and resistant to corrosion, making it ideal for heavy-duty
                                    applications. Our iron products are available in a range of grades and
                                    specifications, making them suitable for both light-duty and heavy-duty
                                    applications. Whether you're working on a construction project, manufacturing
                                    equipment, or repairing machinery, we have the right iron products to meet your
                                    needs.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">In addition to its practical uses, iron is also an
                                    environmentally
                                    friendly material, as it is highly recyclable. Recycling iron reduces the need for
                                    new mining, which helps conserve natural resources and minimizes environmental
                                    impact. We offer iron products that are sourced from sustainable and responsible
                                    suppliers, ensuring that you get high-quality materials while also supporting
                                    environmentally responsible practices. Choose iron for your next project and take
                                    advantage of its strength, versatility, and sustainability for a wide variety of
                                    applications.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_steel_details" name="Steel Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Steel</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735649748/arizogroup/steel-frame-420722_fzyn5g.jpg'"
                                 alt="Steel" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Steel is a versatile and durable alloy made primarily of iron and carbon. Renowned
                                    for its high tensile strength and ability to withstand heavy loads, steel is a
                                    cornerstone material in numerous industries, from construction to manufacturing. Its
                                    resistance to deformation under stress and its ability to be molded into various
                                    shapes make it indispensable for creating structural frameworks, machinery, and
                                    transportation systems.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Beyond strength, steel offers excellent corrosion resistance when alloyed with
                                    elements like chromium to create stainless steel. This makes it suitable for
                                    environments exposed to moisture or harsh conditions. Its recyclability further
                                    underscores its environmental appeal, as repurposed steel retains its original
                                    properties without degradation.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    From reinforcing buildings and bridges to producing household tools and appliances,
                                    steel's adaptability is unmatched. Specialized grades of steel are engineered to
                                    meet specific demands, such as high heat resistance in industrial furnaces or
                                    lightweight properties for automotive parts. With its combination of strength,
                                    flexibility, and sustainability, steel continues to play a pivotal role in advancing
                                    modern infrastructure and technology.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_aluminium_details" name="Aluminium Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Aluminium</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735649747/arizogroup/863681_O6DXDX0_hwphrc.jpg'"
                                 alt="Aluminium" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Aluminium is a lightweight yet robust metal renowned for its corrosion resistance
                                    and versatility. Its remarkable strength-to-weight ratio makes it an essential
                                    material across industries like aerospace, automotive, and construction.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Unlike heavier metals, aluminium is easy to handle and transport, offering reduced
                                    energy consumption during processing and application. Its natural oxide layer
                                    provides exceptional protection against environmental degradation, extending its
                                    lifespan even in challenging conditions.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Aluminium is also highly recyclable, retaining its original properties after
                                    reprocessing. This feature, combined with its adaptability and efficiency, has
                                    established it as a sustainable choice for modern manufacturing needs.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_copper_details" name="Copper Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Copper</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735649749/arizogroup/copper-1504098_mus7g3.jpg'"
                                 alt="Copper" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Copper is a highly conductive metal that has been a cornerstone of technological
                                    advancements for centuries. Its exceptional thermal and electrical conductivity
                                    makes it indispensable in the manufacturing of electrical wiring, motors, and
                                    transformers.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    In addition to its electrical properties, copper is also widely used in plumbing
                                    systems due to its resistance to corrosion and bacteriostatic properties, which help
                                    maintain water quality. This metal’s malleability and ductility allow it to be
                                    formed into various shapes, ensuring its utility in diverse applications.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Beyond industrial uses, copper is celebrated for its aesthetic appeal in
                                    architectural elements, jewelry, and art. Its natural patina adds a distinctive look
                                    over time, making it a timeless material for decorative purposes.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_brass_details" name="Brass Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Brass</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/a_90/v1735649751/arizogroup/pexels-karolina-grabowska-5202425_xu2jvk.jpg'"
                                 alt="Brass" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Brass is an alloy of copper and zinc, prized for its durability, corrosion
                                    resistance, and gold-like appearance. Its ability to withstand harsh environmental
                                    conditions makes it ideal for maritime applications, plumbing fixtures, and
                                    decorative hardware.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Known for its excellent acoustic properties, brass is also widely used in the
                                    production of musical instruments like trumpets, trombones, and saxophones. Its
                                    smooth surface and machinability make it suitable for crafting intricate designs and
                                    shapes.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    With its combination of strength, beauty, and versatility, brass remains a material
                                    of choice in various fields, from industrial manufacturing to fine arts and crafts.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_nickel_details" name="Nickel Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Nickel</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735649748/arizogroup/c-lipped-channel-5528517_ahbmxy.jpg'"
                                 alt="Nickel" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Nickel is a versatile and corrosion-resistant metal that plays a vital role in the
                                    production of alloys. Known for its toughness and strength, it is commonly used in
                                    stainless steel, batteries, and coins.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    This metal's resistance to high temperatures and wear makes it ideal for industrial
                                    applications, including jet engines, chemical processing equipment, and electronics.
                                    Nickel-based alloys are especially crucial in the aerospace and energy sectors.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Nickel's versatility and durability ensure its continued importance in modern
                                    industry and technology, making it an essential material for advancing innovation
                                    and sustainability.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_titanium_details" name="Titanium Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Titanium</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735649749/arizogroup/pexels-rolledalloys-metal-supply-8940820_ntkbi4.jpg'"
                                 alt="Titanium" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Titanium is a lightweight yet incredibly strong metal known for its excellent
                                    corrosion resistance and durability. It is a preferred material for aerospace
                                    applications, where strength and low weight are critical.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Beyond aerospace, titanium is widely used in medical implants due to its
                                    biocompatibility and resistance to body fluids. It is also found in high-performance
                                    sports equipment, industrial machinery, and marine applications.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    The unique properties of titanium make it an indispensable material in industries
                                    where performance, longevity, and reliability are paramount.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_zinc_details" name="Zinc Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Zinc</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735708675/large-steel-factory-warehouse_jlz5ie.jpg'"
                                 alt="Zinc" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Zinc is widely recognized for its role in galvanizing steel and iron to prevent
                                    corrosion. This protective coating significantly extends the life of materials
                                    exposed to harsh environments.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    In addition to galvanization, zinc is an essential component in batteries, alloys
                                    such as brass, and die-casting processes for manufacturing complex metal components.
                                    It is also used in building materials and pharmaceutical products.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    With its versatility and cost-effectiveness, zinc continues to play a crucial role
                                    in industrial and commercial applications worldwide.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_tungsten_details" name="Tungsten Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Tungsten</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735710415/Screenshot_2025-01-01_103115_l4c35m.png'"
                                 alt="Tungsten" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Tungsten is renowned for its incredibly high melting point and exceptional strength.
                                    It is commonly used in heavy-duty industrial applications, such as cutting tools,
                                    mining machinery, and high-temperature furnaces.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Its density and hardness make tungsten an essential material in military
                                    applications, aerospace engineering, and the production of electrical filaments for
                                    lighting.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Tungsten's durability and versatility ensure its critical role in industries
                                    requiring materials that can withstand extreme stress and heat.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_tin_details" name="Tin Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Tin</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735708675/high-angle-tall-tin-cans_scyd0r.jpg'"
                                 alt="Tin" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Tin is widely used to coat steel and other metals, providing protection against
                                    corrosion. This application is especially common in the production of food and
                                    beverage containers, ensuring product safety and longevity.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    In addition to its anti-corrosion properties, tin is a vital component in soldering,
                                    where its low melting point allows for easy and secure connections in electronics
                                    and plumbing.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    As a key ingredient in various alloys, such as bronze, tin has played an essential
                                    role in human history and continues to be a valuable resource in modern
                                    manufacturing.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>


    <!-- Cars Template without "Read More" -->
    <template id="card_cars_details" name="Cars Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Cars</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735708679/4019_uq00q2.jpg'"
                                 alt="Cars" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Scrap cars represent a significant source of recyclable materials, particularly
                                    metals like aluminum, copper, and steel. These metals can be extracted and processed
                                    for reuse in various industries, reducing the need for raw material mining. The
                                    recycling process helps conserve natural resources while minimizing environmental
                                    impact.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Beyond their metals, scrap cars may also contain reusable components such as
                                    batteries, catalytic converters, and tires, which can be repurposed or sold in
                                    secondary markets. This makes the recycling of old vehicles an economically and
                                    environmentally sound practice.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    By recycling scrap cars, industries can reduce landfill waste and promote a circular
                                    economy. This process contributes to a sustainable future by ensuring valuable
                                    materials are not wasted but instead reintegrated into manufacturing cycles.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_turnings_details" name="Turnings Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Turnings</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735708677/9377334967_oxnxmi.png'"
                                 alt="Turnings" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Turnings are small chips or shavings of metal generated during machining operations
                                    such as milling, drilling, or grinding. These by-products, though often overlooked,
                                    hold immense value due to the high-quality metal they contain, which can be recycled
                                    into new products.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    The recycling of turnings reduces the demand for virgin materials, conserving energy
                                    and lowering production costs. Industries such as automotive, aerospace, and
                                    manufacturing benefit greatly from this process, as recycled metals maintain similar
                                    properties to freshly mined metals.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Proper handling and recycling of turnings also help mitigate environmental concerns.
                                    When left untreated, these metal scraps can oxidize or contaminate surrounding
                                    environments. Recycling ensures these materials are processed responsibly,
                                    contributing to sustainable industrial practices.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_appliances_details" name="Appliances Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Appliances</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735708674/assortment-dirty-dumped-objects_atyca3.jpg'"
                                 alt="Appliances" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Old household appliances, such as refrigerators, washing machines, and dryers, are
                                    rich sources of recyclable metals like copper, aluminum, and steel. These metals can
                                    be extracted and reused in new manufacturing processes, significantly reducing the
                                    need for raw material mining.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Beyond the metals, appliances also contain valuable components such as motors,
                                    compressors, and wiring that can be repurposed. Proper recycling of appliances
                                    prevents these materials from ending up in landfills, where they may release harmful
                                    substances into the environment.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Recycling household appliances promotes sustainability and supports a circular
                                    economy. By giving these items a second life, industries can conserve resources,
                                    reduce waste, and contribute to a greener future.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_cans_details" name="Cans Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Cans</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/a_90/v1735708673/barrel-165092_1920_swdw9k.jpg'"
                                 alt="Cans" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Recyclable cans, typically made of aluminum or tin-plated steel, are highly valuable
                                    in the recycling industry. Aluminum cans, in particular, are lightweight, durable,
                                    and can be recycled indefinitely without losing their quality.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Recycling cans requires significantly less energy compared to producing new metal
                                    from raw ore. This energy efficiency translates to reduced greenhouse gas emissions
                                    and a lower environmental footprint, making it a key component of sustainable waste
                                    management.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    By recycling cans, industries contribute to resource conservation and reduce
                                    landfill waste. This process helps foster a circular economy, where materials are
                                    reused, benefiting both the environment and the economy.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="card_radiators_details" name="Radiators Details">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div class="container mt-5">
                <h2 class="card-heading-main">Radiators</h2>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                        <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                            <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735708674/radiator-2682468_m3dxph.jpg'"
                                 alt="Radiators" class="card-img-main"
                                 style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Radiators, often made from copper and aluminum, are valuable materials in the
                                    recycling market. These metals are extracted and reused in various industries,
                                    including automotive, construction, and manufacturing.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    Recycling radiators helps reduce the demand for virgin materials, conserving natural
                                    resources and lowering energy consumption. It also prevents valuable metals from
                                    ending up in landfills, promoting a more sustainable waste management approach.
                                </p>
                                <p class="card-text-full">
                                    The process of recycling radiators not only benefits the environment but also
                                    creates economic opportunities. By recovering and reusing these materials,
                                    industries can reduce costs and contribute to a greener, more efficient
                                    manufacturing process.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>


</odoo>
