<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <template id="carbon_steel_sheets_coil_template" name="Carbon Steel Sheets/Coil">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div class="container mt-5">
                    <h2 class="card-heading-main">Carbon Steel Sheets/Coil</h2>
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                            <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                                <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735800210/arizogroup/spring-1084991_a1nctl.jpg'"
                                     alt="Carbon Steel Sheets/Coil"
                                     class="card-img-main"
                                     style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                                <div class="card-body">
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Carbon steel sheets and coils are versatile materials
                                        widely used
                                        in industrial, construction, and manufacturing sectors. These products are known
                                        for their strength and durability, making them suitable for a range of
                                        applications such as automotive panels, structural components, and pipelines.
                                    </p>
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Our carbon steel sheets and coils are available in various
                                        grades
                                        and thicknesses to meet diverse customer requirements. These materials are
                                        processed
                                        with precision to ensure high-quality standards, offering excellent resistance
                                        to wear
                                        and tear under harsh conditions.
                                    </p>
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Whether you need these sheets and coils for small-scale
                                        projects
                                        or large industrial operations, they provide exceptional performance and value
                                        for money. Explore our range and find the perfect fit for your needs.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>

        <template id="pipe_made_of_stainless_steel_template" name="Pipe Made Of Stainless Steel">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div class="container mt-5">
                    <h2 class="card-heading-main">Pipe Made Of Stainless Steel</h2>
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                            <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                                <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735800166/arizogroup/stainless-steel-tubes-manufacturer_pr8jf8.jpg'"
                                     alt="Pipe Made Of Stainless Steel"
                                     class="card-img-main"
                                     style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                                <div class="card-body">
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Stainless steel pipes are an integral part of industrial
                                        and
                                        residential piping systems due to their superior resistance to corrosion and
                                        oxidation.
                                        These pipes offer long-lasting performance in even the most demanding
                                        environments, such as chemical plants, food processing facilities, and water
                                        treatment systems.
                                    </p>
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Our stainless steel pipes are designed to meet stringent
                                        industry
                                        standards, ensuring reliability and safety in all applications. Available in
                                        various diameters and thicknesses, they are perfect for transporting liquids,
                                        gases, and other materials without compromising quality.
                                    </p>
                                    <p class="card-text-full">With excellent heat resistance and a sleek finish, these
                                        pipes are
                                        also used for decorative purposes in modern architecture. Experience the
                                        unparalleled quality and durability of our stainless steel pipes today.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>

        <template id="round_bars_of_stainless_steel_template" name="Round Bars Of Stainless Steel">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div class="container mt-5">
                    <h2 class="card-heading-main">Round Bars Of Stainless Steel</h2>
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                            <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                                <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735812266/arizogroup/Screenshot_2025-01-02_151052_poeatu.png'"
                                     alt="Round Bars Of Stainless Steel"
                                     class="card-img-main"
                                     style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                                <div class="card-body">
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Stainless steel round bars are essential components in
                                        industries
                                        such as construction, automotive, and manufacturing. These bars are crafted for
                                        precision
                                        and strength, making them ideal for producing fasteners, tools, and machine
                                        components.
                                    </p>
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Our stainless steel round bars come in a variety of sizes
                                        and
                                        grades to cater to diverse applications. They are known for their excellent
                                        resistance to
                                        corrosion, heat, and wear, ensuring longevity and performance under extreme
                                        conditions.
                                    </p>
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Whether you are looking for materials for welding,
                                        machining, or
                                        structural purposes, these round bars provide the reliability and quality you
                                        need. Choose
                                        our stainless steel round bars for your next project.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>

        <template id="shapes_of_steel_i_beam_template" name="Shapes Of Steel I Beam">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div class="container mt-5">
                    <h2 class="card-heading-main">Shapes Of Steel I Beam</h2>
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                            <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                                <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735811308/arizogroup/Screenshot_2025-01-02_151005_uiojxq.png'"
                                     alt="Shapes Of Steel I Beam"
                                     class="card-img-main"
                                     style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                                <div class="card-body">
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Steel I Beams are fundamental in modern construction,
                                        offering
                                        structural support and load-bearing capabilities. These beams are designed to
                                        withstand
                                        heavy loads, making them ideal for buildings, bridges, and other large-scale
                                        projects.
                                    </p>
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Our steel I beams are manufactured to precision standards,
                                        ensuring
                                        durability and consistency. Available in a range of sizes and thicknesses, they
                                        meet the
                                        diverse needs of architectural and engineering designs.
                                    </p>
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Whether used in commercial or industrial projects, our
                                        steel I
                                        beams provide reliable performance and safety. Explore our selection to find the
                                        perfect
                                        beam for your next construction endeavor.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>

        <template id="silicon_steels_template" name="Silicon Steels">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div class="container mt-5">
                    <h2 class="card-heading-main">Silicon Steels</h2>
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                            <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                                <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735812267/arizogroup/Screenshot_2025-01-02_151305_b9bw1e.png'"
                                     alt="Silicon Steels"
                                     class="card-img-main"
                                     style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                                <div class="card-body">
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Silicon steels, also known as electrical steels, are
                                        specially
                                        engineered materials used primarily in electrical and magnetic applications.
                                        These steels
                                        are ideal for manufacturing transformers, electric motors, and generators, as
                                        they offer
                                        exceptional magnetic properties and energy efficiency.
                                    </p>
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Our silicon steels are designed to reduce energy losses,
                                        providing
                                        excellent performance even in high-frequency applications. These materials are
                                        available
                                        in different grades to meet the specific requirements of various electrical
                                        equipment
                                        manufacturers.
                                    </p>
                                    <p class="card-text-full">By choosing our silicon steels, you ensure the reliability
                                        and
                                        efficiency of your electrical systems. These steels contribute significantly to
                                        energy
                                        savings and the overall performance of modern electrical devices.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>

        <template id="stainless_steel_coils_template" name="Stainless Steel Coils">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div class="container mt-5">
                    <h2 class="card-heading-main">Stainless Steel Coils</h2>
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                            <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                                <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735812264/arizogroup/Screenshot_2025-01-02_151353_nsffzm.png'"
                                     alt="Stainless Steel Coils"
                                     class="card-img-main"
                                     style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                                <div class="card-body">
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Stainless steel coils are versatile materials widely used
                                        across
                                        various industries, including construction, automotive, and kitchenware
                                        manufacturing.
                                        These coils are highly durable and resistant to corrosion, making them ideal for
                                        applications in harsh environments.
                                    </p>
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Our stainless steel coils are available in multiple grades
                                        and
                                        finishes, ensuring they meet the unique demands of diverse projects. These coils
                                        are
                                        known for their excellent formability, strength, and aesthetic appeal.
                                    </p>
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Whether you need stainless steel coils for decorative
                                        purposes or
                                        industrial use, our high-quality products are tailored to deliver exceptional
                                        performance
                                        and long-lasting durability. Explore our range today!
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>

        <template id="stainless_steel_h_beams_template" name="Stainless Steel H-Beams">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div class="container mt-5">
                    <h2 class="card-heading-main">Stainless Steel H-Beams</h2>
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-md-12 mb-4">
                            <div class="card shadow-sm text-center">
                                <img t-att-src="'https://res.cloudinary.com/drw030kab/image/upload/v1735812265/arizogroup/Screenshot_2025-01-02_151509_kyv6tf.png'"
                                     alt="Stainless Steel H-Beams"
                                     class="card-img-main"
                                     style="width: 70%; height: 40%; object-fit: cover;"/>
                                <div class="card-body">
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Stainless steel H-beams are essential components in
                                        structural
                                        engineering, offering superior strength and corrosion resistance. These beams
                                        are widely
                                        used in construction, bridges, and large-scale infrastructure projects for their
                                        load-
                                        bearing capabilities.
                                    </p>
                                    <p class="card-text-full">Our stainless steel H-beams are available in various
                                        dimensions and
                                        grades, ensuring they meet the specific needs of your projects. These beams are
                                        designed
                                        to provide optimal performance and safety in challenging environments.
                                    </p>
                                    <p class="card-text-full">By choosing our stainless steel H-beams, you invest in
                                        materials
                                        that ensure the longevity and stability of your structures. Explore our range to
                                        find the
                                        perfect fit for your construction requirements.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>

    </data>
</odoo>
